<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fashion App</string>
    <string name="details1">A T-shirt (or t shirt, or tee) is a style of unisex fabric shirt named after the T shape of its body and sleeves. It normally has short sleeves and a round neckline, known as a crew neck, which lacks a collar. T-shirts are generally made of a stretchy, light and inexpensive fabric and are easy to clean.</string>
    <string name="details4">The Chapeau à la Paméla, Pamela hat or Pamela bonnet described a type of straw hat or bonnet popular during the 1790s and into the first three quarters of the 19th century. It was named after the heroine of 1741 novel Pamela of Samuel Richardson; or, Virtue Rewarded.</string>
    <string name="details3">vest. noun. English Language Learners Definition of vest (Entry 2 of 2) : a sleeveless piece of clothing with buttons down the front that is worn over a shirt and under a suit jacket. : a special piece of clothing that you wear on your upper body for protection or safety.</string>
    <string name="details2">Jeans are a type of pants or trousers, typically made from denim or dungaree cloth. ... Prior to the Levi Strauss patented trousers, the term "blue jeans" had been long in use for various garments (including trousers, overalls, and coats), constructed from blue-colored denim.</string>
    <string name="details5">A belt is a flexible band or strap, typically made of leather or heavy cloth, and worn around the waist, which is usually of less circumference than the hips underneath, preventing pants from falling. A belt supports trousers or other articles of clothing.</string>
    <string name="details6">A poncho (Spanish pronunciation: [ˈpontʃo]; punchu in Quechua; Mapudungun pontro, blanket, woolen fabric) is an outer garment designed to keep the body warm. A rain poncho is made from a watertight material designed to keep the body dry from the rain.</string>
    <string name="details7">An 18th-century garment for women that is similar to a vest of men, usually worn with a riding habit. a body of men garment, often quilted and embroidered and having sleeves, worn under the doublet in the 16th and 17th centuries.</string>
    <string name="details8">A sock is an item of clothing worn on the feet and often covering the ankle or some part of the calf. Some type of shoe or boot is typically worn over socks. In ancient times, socks were made from leather or matted animal hair. ... One of the roles of socks is absorbing perspiration.</string>
</resources>
